Actually, from that moment on,
其实从那个时候开始
I've already had feelings for you.
我就已经喜欢你了
I'm jumping now!
我跳了啊
Go ahead.
放心跳
I've been eating a bit too much lately.
最近吃得有点多
You have to catch me.
你可得接住啊
Don't worry.
放心
I'm strong enough to catch three of you.
三个你都接得住
Come on.
来
Give me your hand.
手
Oopsy!
不好意思啊
I'm just too heavy.
太胖了
That's why you couldn't catch me.
害你没接住
It's OK.
没事
Ling Weiyi!
凌惟依
You've got to say yes to him!
不答应不行啊
We, business school totally
咱经管赢比赛
owes the win to Qi Yu,
靠的可全都是
our aid.
齐郁这个外援
Guys, that's a beauty trick, a cheap shot!
你们这怎么使美人计呢
It's cool, Weiyi.
没事惟依
Just say no to him.
不答应
Next year, we
明年让齐郁
will bring Qi Yu onboard
支援我们数科
and we'll kick your butts!
我们干翻你们
Whether you win or lose the game
你们赢不赢比赛
doesn't concern me.
跟我有什么关系啊
Anyway, I'll support
反正齐郁在哪个队
whatever team Qi Yu is on.
我就支持哪个队
Whoever has him will win!
总归是会赢的呀
Does that count as a "yes"?
这是算答应了吗
Not so fast!
你等一下
Do you really like me?
你是真的喜欢我吗
Will you treat me better than
那你会
anyone else in the world?
全天下第一对我好吗
Of course!
当然了
OK then.
行吧
Do you still like me?
你还喜欢我吗
If you like me, then you do.
喜欢就喜欢
If you don't, then you don't.
不喜欢就不喜欢
Stop dragging it out.
磨磨叽叽
That's not like you at all.
可不像你的风格
I'm sorry.
对不起
Honestly, I want to
其实我每天
call you to apologize every day.
都想打电话给你道歉
But I've realized that
但是我发现
this time, an apology might not work.
这次好像道歉没有用
You don't need to apologize to me.
你不用跟我道歉
You haven't done anything wrong.
你又没有做错什么
It's just that we have
只是我们之间
some issues between us.
确实出现了一些问题
Actually, we
其实我们
don't necessarily have to
也并不是一定要
resolve these issues,
解决这些问题
right?
对吧
I like you,
我喜欢你
and you like me.
你也喜欢我
So why do we have to
那为什么我们每天都要
sulk every day,
苦大仇深地
worrying about
去考虑那些
money,
钱啊
houses,
房子啊
and all those issues?
这些现实问题的
Can't we just love each other
我们就相爱一天
and enjoy a passionate romance?
热恋一天不好吗
This way,
这样
I don't have to change myself,
我不用改变自己
and you
你呢
don't have to
也不用让自己
bear such great pressure.
承受那么大的心理压力
Right?
对不对
Weiyi,
惟依
I understand you're unhappy with this,
我知道你不甘心
but I'm even more dissatisfied.
我更不甘心
But I can't help
但我不可能
think about our future.
不考虑我们的未来
But who can really predict the future?
可是未来谁说得清啊
Let's just live for the present,
我们就过一天
and be happy for the present.
开心一天不好吗
We agreed on this before!
我们之前都说好了的呀
To watch the sunrise and sunset together.
要一起看日出日落
If it rains,
下雨了
we'll cozy up at home and watch movies.
就窝在家里看电影
If it's sunny, we'll go hiking.
天晴了就出去郊游
Surfing in the summer,
夏天去冲浪
skiing in the winter.
冬天去滑雪
If I couldn't fall asleep at night,
要是晚上睡不着觉呢
you'll go to the beach with me.
你就夜里陪我去看海
Isn't that kind of life wonderful?
这样的日子难道不好吗
We can't just
我们不可能一辈子
be in love forever without facing reality.
只谈恋爱不考虑现实
If there's no future,
没有未来的话
I'm just wasting your time.
我就是在耽误你时间
So,
所以
you've already made up your mind
你早就想好
that you want to break up with me, right?
要和我分开了对吗
Ling Weiyi,
凌惟依
let's break up.
我们分手吧
You deserve someone better.
你值得更好的人
And I'm not the
而我对你来说
right person for you.
不是
I remember we
我记得
watched a show before.
咱们之前看过一部
Autumn in My...
蓝色生
Stop it!
你干吗
Are you so eager to find another girl?
你这么想找下家吗
That show was a tragedy, right?
那部剧是个悲剧是吧
But I believe
但是我相信
we will definitely not end up like that.
我们绝对不会像那样
You will be good,
你会好好地
and I will be good too.
我也会好好地
We will always
我们都会
be together.
一直一直在一起
Never apart.
永远不分开
Why did you only run
今天怎么就
for half an hour today?
跑了半个小时啊
I already ran for an hour
你来之前我已经
before you arrived.
跑了一个小时了
I was hoping to
本来想着呀
exhaust myself,
把身体搞垮
so I wouldn't be so heart-broken.
心里就不会那么难受
But I realized that the more tired I get,
结果发现呢
the more I crave someone to lean on.
越累越是想找个人依靠
Come on.
来
Lean on me.
靠着
I'm really glad you're here.
还好有你在
But aren't you supposed to be
但你今天是不是
finding new clients again
那个姓付的人渣那事
because of that scum Mr. Fu?
得重新去找客户啊
Isn't being here with me
你在这儿陪我
taking up your time?
不会耽误你时间吗
My bestie just went through a breakup.
我最好的闺蜜失恋了
I won't be able to concentrate on work.
我还工作什么呀
Forget about work.
工作都靠边站
Even if a
就算现在有一个
billion-dollar client comes knocking,
十个亿的客户找我
I won't be going to work.
我都不会出去工作的
My only priority today
我今天唯一的工作
is to be here with you.
就是陪着你
If it's a billion-dollar client,
十几个亿的大客户
you definitely should go!
那你肯定得去啊
What if your bestie
不然你这闺蜜
ends up breaking up again
万一这两个月
in the next couple of months?
就失恋一回
You'd miss out on the chance
那你不得错过
to become the world's richest person.
当全球首富的机会啊
Can you stop being so negative?
你能不能不要乌鸦嘴啊
This breakup
这次失恋
is your last one.
就是你最后一次了
The next guy you are going out with
下次遇到的
will definitely be someone
一定是一个
who genuinely cares for you,
非常喜欢你
and treats you right,
对你又好
someone who can share a lifetime with you.
可以跟你厮守终生
As for this time,
这一次嘛
let's just chalk it up to a regret.
就算是个遗憾吧
You know, in a lifetime,
你说人这一辈子
how can anyone go without regrets?
哪能没有遗憾呢
Having no regrets at all
一点遗憾都没有
would be rather dull,
也挺没意思的
don't you think?
是不是
Let me grab my phone.
我拿下手机
Xiaoning,
小涂
your friend, Mr. Yu
你那个朋友余总
made a significant deposit today.
今天来办理了大笔存款
The clients
你这几天
you've secured recently
跑下的几个客户
are also moving into the approval process.
也都进入审批流程了
We've hit the target for this month.
这个月业绩拿下
You can relax and take your annual leave.
你可以安心休个年假了
And enjoy some quality time
和你的新婚老公
with your new husband.
好好出去玩玩
I'm really sorry, Mr. Ji.
对不起了纪先生
My bestie is going through a tough time.
在我最好的朋友面前
You should take a back seat for now.
你还是先靠边站吧
Lean on me.
靠着
Where do you want to go?
想去哪儿玩
I'll take some time off soon.
我现在有假期了
Wherever you feel like going, I'm down.
你想去哪儿咱就去哪儿
I want to go alone.
我想一个人去
That's not an option.
那不行
I can't let you do that.
我不放心
I had been with Qi Yu
我跟齐郁
for so many years.
这么多年
We had been through so much together.
一起经历了这么多事
I think it's time for me to
我也是时候
spend some time alone
该一个人
to really sort things out.
好好地整理一下了
Don't worry about me.
放心吧
I won't be
我呢
single forever.
不可能一直单过的
I won't do anything rash either.
更不会想不开
Once I'm feeling better,
等我好起来了
I'll find my way back.
我自己就会回来的
Just like I did last time.
像上次一样
Someone mentioned back then
某些人当时可是说过
that whenever she had a vacation,
只要有假呢
she would go spend some quality time
就要跟他们家纪先生
with her Mr. Ji.
一起去度假
Alright, don't worry about me.
好啦别担心我啦
I just want to take some time for myself.
就想自己好好待会儿
How could I possibly not
你说怎么能让人
worry about you?
不担心啊
I've been waiting for you for a while.
我等你半天了
I have some exciting news.
新鲜出炉的好消息
The loan for the new energy company
你亲自出马谈下的
that you personally negotiated with
新能源企业
is already in the approval process.
融资已经在走审批啦
As long as we secure this
只要这个
top-tier client,
首屈一指的大客户拿下
It will lay a solid foundation for
也算给咱们
the future development of
集安分行未来发展
our Jian branch.
奠定了一个基础
Once we start
等开展业务领域的
comprehensive cooperation
全面合作
with them,
咱未来
we won't have to worry about
相当一段时间的业绩
our performance for a long time.
都不用发愁了
That sounds like great news.
听起来是个好消息
But still, you need to
不过接下来
keep a close watch on everything.
你得盯紧一点了
Don't worry.
放心吧
By the way,
对了
I'm taking the annual leave
我请了一个年假
along with the Mid-Autumn Festival.
连着中秋假期一起
Mr. manager,
赵总
in the coming days,
未来的一段时间里
make sure to pay extra attention.
多上点心
Mr. manager?
赵总
You
你
called me
刚才说
Mr. manager.
赵总
What do you mean by that?
什么意思啊
Hon,
老婆
let me help you put the apron on,
把围腰给你系上啊
so you won't stain your white dress.
免得你这白衣服弄脏了
This is amazing!
太好吃了
I did some research.
我查了资料
Having hot pot occasionally
偶尔吃一两顿火锅
is really not a big deal.
问题不大
Told ya.
早就跟你说了
Also,
而且啊
having some milk tea now and then
偶尔喝个一两杯奶茶
is perfectly fine.
问题也不大
Told you that as well.
我也早就跟你说了
Your milk tea
这奶茶
is almost finished.
快喝完了
I'll get you another one.
我再给你点一杯
Get me a cold one.
给我点个凉的
No way.
不行
Fine, a hot one then.
那行吧热的
It's perfectly fine for me
我吃火锅喝奶茶
to enjoy some hot pot and milk tea,
是没什么问题
but I think you might have a problem.
我倒是觉得你有点问题
What problem do I have?
我有什么问题
Getting promoted to department manager,
升一个部门经理
are you really that excited?
至于这么高兴吗
Did you prepare this
摆这么一大桌
lavish feast just for me?
就是为了我
What else could it be?
那不然呢
To put it grandly,
往大了说啊
my career
我的事业
has reached a significant milestone.
取得了阶段性成功
To put it simply, at home,
往小了说以后在家里面
I can finally stand on equal footing
我终于能和饶总
with Ms. Rao.
平起平坐了
Congrats.
恭喜
This is a huge occasion.
这么大的喜事
Hot pot and
你别说吃顿火锅
milk tea would be nothing.
喝杯奶茶了
Even if you want to hit the club tonight
就算今天晚上
and check out some hot dudes,
你想上夜店看黄毛帅哥
I'd greenlight it.
我也奉陪到底
I didn't do it last time, seriously.
上次我没看
Now that sounds more like it!
这还差不多
Besides, those dudes
再说那黄毛帅哥
can't hold a candle to my charm.
哪有你老公耐看
Exactly!
就是
Come on,
来
have a piece of meat.
吃块肉肉
I've had a ton. You dig in.
我好多了你快吃
I knew it.
我就知道
Yuheng is
老纪这个人做事
always reliable
一向很地道
and never makes empty promises.
不会乱画饼的
You're still
你还在这儿
praising him to the skies, huh?
跟我吹老纪的彩虹屁呢
You still don't realize that
就你还不知道
he promoted you
人家老纪
to department manager
让你当部门经理
just so he could
为的就是
offload all the work onto you
把所有的事情都推给你
and then enjoy
然后呢
his annual leave
休着年假
with his
带自己的新媳妇
newlywed wife.
快活去了
Where's my milk tea?
我的奶茶呢
Did you order it?
你点了吗
Nope,
不点了
too much milk tea isn't good for you.
奶茶喝多了对身体不好
Believe it or not, I'll pour
信不信这火锅底料
this whole thing on your face.
倒你脸上
It's already on the way.
已经在路上了
Dig in.
接着吃
Hello there!
你好
Could you please take a photo
帮我和我老婆
for my wife and me?
拍张照片吧
- Thanks. - Sure.
谢谢 可以啊
No problem.
可以
Let's take a photo.
咱俩合个影
You two, come a bit closer.
二位靠近点
Smile!
笑甜蜜一点
Let's see how it looks.
看看怎么样
Looks fantastic. Thanks.
拍得很好看谢谢你啊
What do you think?
你看怎么样
Thanks a lot.
谢谢你啊
No problem.
没事 没事
Mr. Ji mentioned that you can find him
纪先生说通过这只小猫
through this kitty.
就能找到他
Good luck!
加油哦
Let me hold the camera for you.
这我先帮你拿着吧
The story
故事
begins with that kitty.
从那只猫咪开始
Why don't we go back and look for it?
要不我们回去找找吧
It should still be around.
应该还在呢
Never mind.
算了吧
Let's go.
走
I'll get a new one.
再买个新的去
When I was in high school,
我高中的时候
I also used this kind of eraser.
也用这样的橡皮
Take it.
拿着呀
Where did you get this umbrella?
你怎么会有这把伞啊
Isn't this
这把伞
from my dad's company?
不是我爸公司的吗
How come you have one as well?
你怎么会有啊
You remember this umbrella?
你还记得这把伞啊
Of course.
当然了
When my dad was still working,
我爸还上班的时候
his company gave out these umbrellas
他们公司每年发福利
every year as perks.
都有这把伞
We must have had at least
我们家
fifteen of them,
不说二十把
if not twenty.
也有十五把了吧
Do you have any relatives
你们家也有亲戚
working at Puling too?
在浦龄工作啊
So, if the first guy approaching you
那如果高中毕业那年
after high school graduation was me,
第一个走向你的人是我
would you have said yes?
你会答应吗
But in reality,
可是生活里
there are no "ifs".
哪有那么多如果呀
Back then, you didn't even like me.
那个时候你又不喜欢我
Life doesn't have "ifs".
生活里没有如果
So I would still
所以我还是会
be with you.
和你在一起的
If this morning,
如果今天早上
that person wasn't me,
那个人不是我
would you still
你也会
come to her rescue?
跑过去救吗
I would.
会
But if it were someone else,
但如果是别人的话
I would do it as the supervisor.
我是作为上司
But because it was actually you,
因为是你
besides being your supervisor,
除了上司的时间
I'm also your future husband.
我更是你的准老公
Is this how you
这就是你
see yourself?
对自己的评价吗
Tu Xiaoning, you weren't like this before.
涂筱柠你以前不这样
You've changed.
你变了
Yeah, I've changed.
我变了
People do change.
人就是会变的
Just look at yourself.
你看看你现在
You've changed too.
你现在变得
You're no longer the
也不是我一开始认识的
Ji Yuheng I knew.
那个纪昱恒了呀
Honestly, I have
其实我身上
many flaws as well.
也有很多的缺点
I hope that
我希望
if you see
如果你以后看到了
my ordinary side
我的那些平凡
or even my mediocrity,
甚至是平庸的时候
you won't be disappointed in me.
可以不要对我那么失望
And you won't despise me.
也不要嫌弃我
How could I ever despise you?
我怎么会嫌弃你呢
You are Ji Yuheng.
你可是纪昱恒啊
If you like me,
你喜欢我
I am Ji Yuheng.
我才是纪昱恒
If you don't like me,
你要是不喜欢我
I'm just an ordinary folk you see everyday.
我就是一个普通人
When we met again,
再见面时
you gave me a home.
你给了我一个家
Thanks to you,
因为有你
life is no longer a dull black and white.
生活不再是单调的黑白
It's filled with color.
而是有了色彩
I want to make one for our entire family.
做一个大的全家福
With my dad and mom,
有我爸我妈
your dad and mom,
你爸你妈
and the two of us.
还有我们两个
Leave no one behind.
一个都不能少
Thank you, my dear.
谢谢你啊
My Mrs. Ji,
我的纪太太
on our road ahead,
未来的路
please rest assured
请你放心地
to entrust yourself to me.
把自己交给我
I will do everything I can
我一定会尽我所能
to make you happy,
让你幸福
to keep you safe.
让你平安
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
谢谢你啊纪先生
Thank you
谢谢你
for giving me
给了我一个
such a memorable
这么难忘
and beautiful wedding.
美好的婚礼
Thank you
谢谢你
for being a part of my life.
出现在我的生命里
Being with you
跟你在一起
is the happiest thing
是我觉得这辈子
I've ever experienced.
最幸福的事
Mom, dad,
爸妈
today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
今天是中秋节
We came back to see you.
我们回来看你了
By the way, I have some
对了我有一个
exciting news to share with you.
好消息要告诉你们
You're going to be grandparents!
你们要当外公外婆了
I
我呢
am already married
已经结婚了
and have my own family.
有了自己的家
From now on, in this world,
我以后在这个世界上
I'm no longer
再也不是
by myself.
孤孤单单的一个人了
The guy I married
我找的这个人呢
isn't very tall,
个子不是很高
and he's not
长得吧
particularly good looking.
也不是特别帅
He's my colleague,
他是我的同事
and
但是
he loves me deeply.
他很爱我
Of course,
当然了
I love him too.
我也很爱他
It's just that I don't
只是
often bring that up in front of him.
我平时不太跟他说这些
By the way,
对了
last time I came home,
上次我回来的时候
he was also here.
他就在
Did you think
不会是你们
he is the right one,
觉得他比较好
so you sent him
所以把他安排在
to me?
我身边的吧
Of course.
当然了
In your
在老丈人
parents' eyes, I must
和丈母娘的眼里
be the perfect son-in-law.
我肯定是五好女婿
Burn the incense.
上香吧给他们
Mom, dad.
爸 妈
Rest assured.
你们放心
I
我
love Jing with all my heart.
是发自内心地爱着饶静
My parents
我爸爸妈妈
adore her too.
也都很喜欢她
I'll
未来
always be there for her,
我会好好照顾她的
loving her,
用心去爱她
accompanying her,
陪伴她
taking care of her,
照顾她
She won't be alone anymore.
让她也不再孤单
We'll come
以后我们两个人
visit you often.
也会经常回来看你们的
I'm a bit
我这个人啊
of a talker,
就是
please
嘴有点碎
don't mind.
您别嫌我烦
There, there.
别哭了
It's okay.
乖 乖 乖
Okay.
好了
Now.
来
One.
一
Two.
二
Three.
三
Perfect.
好完美
Done.
辛苦两位
I'm beat.
我好累啊
My feet are killing me.
我脚好疼啊
I'm exhausted.
好累啊
Aren't you tired?
你不累吗
You've been lifting
你又是抱我
and carrying me around,
又是背我的
but looks like you're not even phased.
我看你一点感觉都没有
I'm usually
我不是一直
pretty strong, right?
体力都挺好的吗
Excuse me.
不好意思啊
Could you guys do
能不能请你们
a few more sets?
再多拍几组
You're both so good-looking,
我看两位男帅女美的
I'd love to use your photos
想用你们的照片
as sample images for our store
作为我们店的一个展示
and put them online.
投放到网络渠道
Absolutely,
当然了
we'll send you the photos
这个照片做出来
as soon as
我们第一时间
they're done,
一定给你们
and we'll cut the price
而且这个价格
in half for you.
可以给你们打对折
Half?
对折啊
I...
那我
Sorry.
不好意思啊
My wife's feeling a bit worn out,
我太太今天有点累了
so we can't do this favor.
帮不了这个忙
It's okay.
没关系 没关系
We'll respect
这肯定要尊重
your call on this.
你们的个人意愿
Well.
那
Go ahead and change.
二位先去换衣服吧
Thanks for your time.
打扰了
Okay.
好
Thanks.
谢谢啊
The discount
对折啊
is pretty sweet,
还是挺划算的
why'd you pass it up?
为什么不答应啊
I wanna keep your
我不想让别人
beauty all to myself.
看到你的美
You had a different tune
昨天试衣服的时候
yesterday during the fitting.
那个大方劲哪儿去了
I gotta admit,
不过说得也是
I don't wanna share
我也不想让太多人
those hot pics
看到我们家纪先生
of you either.
这么帅的照片
I'll hoard them.
我得自己捂好了
How?
准备怎么捂啊
It's a surprise.
那我不能告诉你
Okay.
好
Thanks for being
谢谢你啊纪先生
so cooperative
今天辛苦了
during the shoot.
这么配合我拍一组照片
I love them.
我可喜欢了
No need to thank me,
这说的什么话呀
we're in this together.
当然不用谢我了
I love you.
爱你哦
You too.
我也是
Xiaoning looks stunning
筱柠穿上婚纱
in her wedding dress.
可真美呀
My little girl's
女儿
all grown up and married now.
女儿终于嫁人了
Okay, okay.
好了 好了 好了
Tu.
老涂
Enough.
好了啊
It's our baby
这女儿结婚
girl's big day.
是高兴的事啊
There, there.
行了 行了
Too bad, my
就是可惜啊
"Magpie Bridge" moment
我的那个鹊桥相会
isn't gonna happen.
是没戏了
Let's go
咱俩去
to that bridge
今年咱俩
on our wedding
结婚纪念日的时候
anniversary
咱去那儿
and
跟
and walk over everyone's
大家的头顶上走过去
heads.
鹊桥相会
How's that sound?
咋样
Sure.
行
And get
咱俩再去
a fresh set of wedding pics.
拍它一组婚纱照怎么样
Yeah.
行
Sure.
就是
I wanna try on a wedding dress,
那我也穿穿婚纱
we missed out on that.
咱结婚的时候就没拍
From...
从那个
Seeing her in white just
难忘 我看着她穿婚纱
gets me choked up.
我还是难过
Okay, okay.
好了 好了 好了
Everything's so familiar,
熟悉的味道
the smell, the place,
熟悉的环境
the sky,
熟悉的天空
the moon...
熟悉的月亮
Buzzing?
兴奋啊
Remember when
你还记得吗
you were
那天啊
spouting off about that
你还跟我讲什么大道理
backpack theory?
背包理论
It's been ages.
这么久了谁还记得
I
我呀
remember it all.
我可都记得
Your funny moment,
这可是你宝贵的黑历史
I'll cherish
以后我要时常
and savor it.
拿出来回味的
You were
你那天还说
all "life's not worth it,"
活着没意义生活无趣
"I envy your freedom" that day.
羡慕我活得自在
Come on,
没劲
just a little joke.
怎么还说不得了呢
Sit.
坐
Sit down.
坐 坐 坐
Let's chat.
再聊会儿嘛
Anything goes, huh?
那就是都能说呗
Yeah.
说
Alright,
那我就说说
let's chat then.
咱们就说说
Later on that night,
那天更以后
some dude got wasted.
也不知道是谁喝多了
Next day, he was too
第二天连床都起不来
hungover to even
完了之后在那个
crawl out of bed.
酒店里边
In the hotel,
直线都走不了
he was doing the S-walk,
完了就那个曲线
like this, this, and this,
就这样 这样 这样
all the way up to the boat.
直到上了船
Okay.
行
Stop.
行了打住
Sorry,
对不起
babe, my bad.
对不起老婆我错了
How about we agree never
那以后咱俩就签订一个
to bring up our goofy past?
黑历史互不相提原则
Just bury
我们把这些
those memories
不堪入目的回忆
deep
统统扔进
and forget
岁月的垃圾箱
about them.
锁起来
Okay?
行吗
No.
不行
Hey, you're the one
让说的也是你
who started it.
不让说的也是你
Who do you think you are,
你以为你是谁
king of the world
世界的中心
or something?
宇宙的尽头啊
You're still at it?
怎么还没完了呢
Just bored, huh?
我看你就是生活无趣
Picking on me for fun.
龇我两句图个热闹
Thanks,
我谢谢你
babe.
我亲爱的老公
You really
因为你呢
know how to
我的生活变得
spice things up.
特别的热闹
I just want
现在的我呀
a little peace now.
就想图个清静
Okay.
好 好 好
Now.
来
Your choice.
你清静啊
I'll zip it.
我闭麦
Hey, how about
你说我们下次
when we're back here
来西海镇的时候
with the baby,
孩子也出生了
we throw a tiny
我们在西海镇
wedding
举办一个婚礼吧
for just us three?
什么人都不请
And let our
就我们三个
little one be our witness.
孩子当我们证婚人
Yeah.
好啊
You're
老婆
the boss.
你做主
I'm all ears.
都听你的
It's
而且
gonna be epic.
这样更有纪念意义
And cost-effective.
还经济实惠
Wedding's cool.
本来挺好一个事
But cost-
你非得往那个
effective?
经济实惠上靠
You're a real
你真是把这个
tightwad,
铁公鸡的人设
aren't you?
贯穿到底啊
Just save where I can.
咱们过日子嘛
You know.
还就
Who is it?
谁啊
My dad.
我爸
Mom, dad.
爸妈
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
爸妈节日快乐
Grabbed a mooncake yet?
吃月饼了吗
Yeah.
吃了 吃了
And you?
你们吃了没
Jing.
静静啊
Fanggang said you're
上次呢方刚打电话
not sleeping well.
说你最近失眠
So, I sent you some
我把咱们家产的那个
homemade jujube powder
酸枣仁哪磨成粉了
from our hometown,
给你寄过去了
all natural.
纯天然的
It'll be there
你们回去了
when you get back.
应该差不多收到了
Why tell them
你怎么
about that?
什么都跟爸妈说呀
It's good for you.
对你好嘛
Jujube really works for sleep.
酸枣仁对失眠有效
It's too much trouble.
你老麻烦他们
Give it a try.
你吃吃看
Maybe your
睡眠不好
sleep issues are from stress.
可能是精神压力太大
If you
等周末
you have time this weekend,
你们有时间就回来
come here and
我们带你们
we'll take you around
四处玩一玩
to relax a bit.
放松 放松
Thanks.
谢谢爸妈
And sorry,
还有对不起啊爸妈
Fanggang
现在
and I should have been there with you
我应该跟方刚回去
for Mid-Autumn Festival.
陪你们团圆的
Silly girl.
傻孩子
It's not a big deal.
这有啥对不起的
Visiting your parents'
你们回去祭拜亲家
grave is priority.
这是正事
Family's family,
咱们是一家人
every get-together
不分什么节日不节日的
is special,
啥时候见面
right?
就是团圆
And
再说了
look up,
抬头看看
we're all under the same moon.
还不都是同一个月亮吗
Yeah.
就是
Right.
对
Dad.
爸
Look.
你们看
The moon's
爸这月亮
great, right?
行吧
I'll let you go now.
就说到这儿吧
Dad.
爸
Easy on the mooncakes.
你少吃点月饼啊
Watch your blood sugar.
你血糖高
Gotta go.
先挂了
Bye.
拜拜
What's up?
怎么了
Nothing.
没什么
Feels good
就是觉得
to have family,
有家人挺好的
to have you.
有你也挺好的
And when you smile, it's
而且你笑起来也挺好的
beautiful.
特别美
Hold that grin.
就是这样
I'm getting a shot.
我给你拍照
The pretty smile.
美的一刻要记录下来
Hold it,
别动啊
don't move.
保持住啊
Get the baby in the frame.
把他也拍进去
Alright.
来
Okay.
好
Three.
三
Two.
二
One.
一
One more.
再来一张
Three.
三
Two.
二
One.
一
And a selfie.
咱们再自拍一张
Three.
三
Two.
二
One.
一
Gonna post it to Moments.
我发个朋友圈啊
Their wedding pics?
他们都拍婚纱照了
Give it a like.
我赶紧点个赞
You see?
看啊
Talents entwined,
一双两好
beauty and brains,
才子佳人
a union divine,
郎才女貌
love that remains.
百年偕老
With that mouth of gold,
你就不应该当客户经理
you should be
你嘴皮子这么溜
on stage,
你该去那个
not behind a desk.
乡村大集上走穴串台
You're a comedic gem.
活脱脱一个显眼包
You're just
羡慕
green with
嫉妒
envy.
恨
Of my golden mouth
你就是羡慕我
and
口才好
my rhymes.
单押成双
What's up?
怎么啦
I think...
我好像
What?
怎么了
I'm getting
我 我 我
some kicks in there.
我好像胎动了
Really?
是胎动了吗
You hear that?
你听见了吗
Yeah.
听见了
Babe.
老婆
I feel it.
我感受到了
Stay strong, little one.
宝宝你好好的
You're
你马上就要
almost here,
来这个世界上了
and we're gonna
爸爸妈妈都会
love you to pieces.
很爱很爱你的
Listen, don't copy your dad's
你呀千万别跟你爸学的
smooth-talking ways.
嘴皮子这么溜
Stick to your books
一定要好好学习
and forget about
咱不能去那个大集上
stand-up.
走穴串台啊
I love you, babe.
我爱你老婆
I love you.
我也爱你
Happy Wedding.
新婚快乐
Tu Xiaoning.
涂筱柠
At least one of us is happy,
还好我们俩之间
that's what counts.
起码有一个人是幸福的
It's nice.
真好
Will I see
也不知道今天
the sunrise today?
能不能有日出呢
Morning.
早啊
Morning, boss.
行长早
Morning, Tu.
小涂姐早
Over the next month,
接下来的一个月
I'm gonna go through
我打算对我们行的
our corporate accounts,
对公账户进行一下梳理
explore their funding needs,
挖掘他们资金需求
and then offer some
然后有针对性地
tailored services.
进行一些服务
Well.
那
Yuan Lang.
元朗
Tingting.
亭亭
And Xiaoning's apprentice.
还有我们筱柠的徒弟
You three,
你们三个
just work well
就负责
together with your boss.
配合好你们的领导
No problem.
没问题
You're all about the lobby,
最近一心扑在大堂上
leaving BDD
我们拓展部
in the dust?
你就撒手不管了
BDD has you, Manager Zhao.
你这个赵总又不是摆设
Think
怎么
you can't cut it?
干不好啊
I
干嘛
got this.
肯定能干好
But show some love to BDD, will ya?
但你多少关注一下吗
By the way.
对了
Got a client
今天下午
meeting this afternoon.
我要约见一个客户
Come with me.
陪我一起去
You got jobs for me?
开始给我派活儿了啊
Just make sure you're on board.
我这是向上管理
Tu.
小涂
You...
这
Hustling hard
刚上调职位
after the promotion, huh?
就这么拼命啊
You're really outdoing yourself,
以前觉得静姐卷
even Jing can't keep up
现在跟你比起来啊
with your work ethic.
就是小巫见大巫
Aw, come on.
你可别这么说啊
You're flattering me.
你这太抬举我了
I'm no match for Jing.
我跟静姐可比不了
Almost time.
快一点了
I have a client
我约了一点钟
meeting at 1.
见客户
Early bird catches the worm.
笨鸟得先飞
I gotta go.
我走了啊
Okay.
好 好 好
Grab my tray, will ya?
帮我收一下啊
You got it.
加油
Mr. Liu.
刘总
This is Mr. Ji,
这是我们
the President of Ji'an Branch.
集安分行的纪行长
Mr. Ji.
纪行长
Heard so much about you.
久闻大名啊
Hello.
你好
I'm Ji Yuheng.
我是纪昱恒
This way.
这边请
You remember
涂经理没忘了
today's the big day, right?
今天是什么日子吧
Bye.
慢走
Of course.
当然
Anniversary
是不是
feels simpler than
跟去年的婚礼比起来
the wedding,
今年这个纪念日
yeah?
有点简陋了
Nah.
不会啊
Just us two, together,
只要我们两个在一起
it's all good.
就是最好的纪念日
So, Mrs. Ji, how's married life
但还是想问一下纪太太
treating you this year?
这一年的婚姻生活
Satisfied?
还满意吗
Yeah.
满意
Just simple,
虽然平凡
but super happy.
但是超级幸福
Mr. Ji.
纪先生
Got any visions
你对咱们俩
for our married life
未来的婚姻生活
ahead?
有什么展望吗
I just want
我当然是希望
every day to be
未来的每一天
like this
都能像现在这样
simple
平凡
but super
但是却又
happy.
很幸福
It will be.
一定会的